One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Big News
‫الأنباء الصادمة‬
Pangaea Castle Mary Geoise
‫مـاريـجـوا‬ ‫قلعة بانجيا‬
The World Conference, also known as the Reverie...
‫المؤتمر العالمي «ليفيلي.»‬
is a grand assembly of fifty kings and queens
‫إنّه مؤتمر كبير يضمّ 50 ممثلًا من ملوك وملكات يُعقد كل أربع سنوات،‬
As always, the Reverie concluded in a state of great confusion
‫فُضَّ مؤتمر «ليفيلي» في حالة ارتباك كبير كالعادة،‬
and all the representatives returned home.
‫عاد كلّ الممثّلين إلى بلدانهم.‬
Then...
‫ومن ثمّ...‬
one week later...
‫مرَّ أسبوع...‬
Good grief... I'm finally home.
‫يا إلهي... عدتُ للدّيار أخيرًا-جامون...‬
Ryugu Palace, Ryugu Kingdom Fishman Island
‫جزيرة البرمائيين‬ ‫قلعة ريوغو‬ ‫بمملكة ريوغو‬
Truly, the surface world is so far above us.
‫إنّ العالم السّطحيّ على مسافة طويلة فوقنا حقًّا...‬
Um, thank you so much for escorting us,
‫عذرًا، شكرًا لك على مرافقتنا‬
Sir Luffy's grandfather!
‫يا جدّ لوفي-ساما!‬
It was a pretty long trip, huh, Neptune?
‫كانت رحلة طويلة، صحيح يا نبتون؟‬
You must be tired!
‫لا بدّ أنّك متعب!‬
I'm exhausted.
‫أنا منهك-جامون.‬
Garp, stay here with us and replenish your energy.
‫ابقَ هنا معنا واسترح جيّدًا يا غارب.‬
Well, maybe I'll have a cup of tea,
‫حسنٌ، سأحتسي كوب شاي‬
but considering the situation, I can't stay here for long.
‫لكن نظرًا للوضع الحاليّ، لن أبقى طويلًا...‬
The Reverie always triggers big incidents.
‫إنّ مؤتمر «ليفيلي» يسبّب الحوادث دائمًا.‬
When fifty countries gather, a simple "let's get along" won't suffice.
‫حين يجتمع خمسين بلدًا لن تجدي عبارة «لنتّفق معًا» نفعًا.‬
Each of them has their own internal troubles.
‫لكلّ بلاد مشكلاتٍ عدة تخصّها.‬
Large and mighty countries just stare quietly at each other
‫تحدّق البلدان الكبيرة والقويّة إلى بعضها في صمت،‬
and let their proxies bicker.
‫وتدع وكلاءها يتشاجرون...‬
They use resources and technologies as leverage.
‫بالنسبة لها فالموارد والتقنيات يعدّون نفوذًا.‬
They say that all countries are on equal footing, but that's just talk.
‫يُقال إنّ كلّ البلدان متساوية لكنّها محض وعود كاذبة‬
Wealth, poverty, and religious differences won't allow them to be equal.
‫الثروة والفقر والاختلافات الدينية لن تسمح بتحقيق المساواة فيما بينها...‬
Even if they appear to shake hands and smile, they'll gladly step on each other's feet.
‫حتّى إن تصافحوا تجدهم يضمرون الضغائن لبعضهم خلف ابتسامة‬
I wonder how many leaders can speak for both their citizens and those of other countries.
‫أتساءل كم ملك بوسعه الحديث باسم مواطنيه والبلدان الأخرى...‬
It's only a roundtable in name.
‫لا بدّ أنّ الطاولة المستديرة تتحسّر عليهم...‬
You're right. Conversations among the sovereigns were touch and go.
‫معك حقّ، فقد كانت المحادثات بين القادة ملتهبة‬
We're no exception, but quarrels between countries can't be solved so easily.
‫ونحن لا نُستثنى منها، لكنّ المشاحنات بين البلدان ليست سهلة الحل‬
The further a country's history extends,
‫إن وُجد تاريخ طويل،/ فلا بدّ أنّ للصّراع جذورًا أعمق‬
Even if there is a disagreement, as long as no blood is spilled, I call it peace.
‫حتّى إن كانت هنالك خلافات، فسأسمّي ما بينهم سلامًا ما دام لم تُرَق الدّماء.‬
But what happened this time was pretty bad...
‫لكنّ ما جرى هذه المرّة كارثي!‬
This may be coming a bit late, but there's one thing I haven't told you about yet.
‫ربّما فات الأوان على قول هذا، لكن ثمّة أمرًا واحدًا في الحقيقة لم أخبرك به‬
Right after the Reverie was dismissed and we set off, an incident occurred,
‫وقعت حادثة ما بعد أن فُضّ المؤتمر مباشرةً وانطلقنا مغادرين‬
I received a report while aboard our ship.
‫وتلقّيت التقرير على متن السفينة.‬
We Marines will do our best to resolve it, but please don't fear
‫سنبذل نحن البحريّة قصارى جهدنا لحلّها، لكن أرجوكم لا تخافوا...‬
the surface world or us humans!
‫من العالم السطحي أو البشر!‬
An incident...?
‫ما الذي جرى؟‬
Garp, what kind of report did you receive?
‫ما التقرير الذي تلقّيته يا غارب؟‬
The incident concerns the Kingdom of Alabasta.
‫إنّها حادثةٌ تخصّ مملكة أرباستا.‬
The Kingdom of Alabasta...
‫مملكة أرباستا...‬
Princess Vivi!
‫فيفي-ساما!‬
Before all of this transpired...
‫قبل حدوث كلّ هذا...‬
At the World Economic News, right after the Reverie was dismissed...
‫في صحيفة الاقتصاد العالمية بعد فضّ مؤتمر «ليفيلي» مباشرة...‬
Unbelievable! It's incident after incident!
‫مذهل، الحوادث تأتي متتاليةً!‬
I can't believe so much happened at once...
‫لا أصدّق أنّ كلّ هذه الأشياء حدثت دفعةً واحدة.‬
Listen up! Find me the greatest headline yet!
‫اسمعوا، فكّروا في أفضل العناوين على الإطلاق!‬
Sir, which one should make the front page?!
‫أيّ المواضيع سيكون عنوان صحيفتنا الرئيسي أيها الرئيس؟‬
Listen! We have a death on our hands!
‫أنصتوا، ثمّة من مات!‬
Editor-in-Chief Morgans World Economic Newspaper
‫رئيس تحرير صحيفة‬ ‫الاقتصاد العالمية‬ ‫مورغانز‬
Big obituaries move papers!
‫تُباع صحف أكثر عندما تحتوي نعيًا ضخمًا!‬
Then, the headli–
‫إذًا فالعنوان الرئيسي هو...‬
No, wait!
‫كلّا، انتظري!‬
The resolution they passed is also good.
‫القرار الّذي وافقوا عليه جيّد أيضًا.‬
But a murder attempt is exciting as well!
‫لكنّ خبر محاولة ارتكاب جريمة قتل سيشعل الحماس!‬
That's right!
‫معك حق‬
Okay, let's have two front pages!
‫حسنٌ، لنضع صفحتان رئيسيّتا وستكون الصّفحة الخلفيّة بنفس تصميم الأولى‬
– Okay!
‫حسنًا!‬
Sir.
‫أيها الرئيس،‬
Express mail from the government.
‫بريد عاجل من الحكومة‬
A check, huh?
‫شيك إذًا؟‬
Oh, that's a lot!
‫هذا مبلغ كبير!‬
I see. It's an order to manipulate information.
‫فهمت، إنّه أمر للتّلاعب بالمعلومات.‬
But for which affair?
‫لكن لصالح أيّ قضيّة؟‬
Hushing up this incident?!
‫يريدون التّكتّم عن الحادثة؟‬
No way in hell!
‫هذا من سابع المستحيلات!‬
Throw this back in their faces!
‫ارمهِ على وجوههم.‬
Hey, what's wrong?
‫ما الخطب يا هذا؟‬
My, my, my...
‫لا، لا، لا...‬
Do as you're told, Morgans!
‫نَفِّذ ما يُملى عليك يا مورغانز!‬
The secret agency,
‫الوكالة السرية،‬
Cipher Pol?!
‫سايفر بول؟!‬
You must obey orders from the World Government.
‫عليك الانصياع لأوامر حكومة العالم.‬
Don't move!
‫لا تتحركوا!‬
Never underestimate Big News Morgans!
‫لا تستخفّ بمورغانز صاحب الأنباء الصادمة!‬
When did he sneak in?
‫متى تسلّل إلى هنا؟!‬
Sir! Members of Cipher Pol are government officials!
‫إنّ أعضاء سايفر بول ضبّاط في الحكومة أيها الرئيس!‬
I know!
‫أعلم ذلك!‬
It's dangerous to stay here, guys.
‫من الخطير البقاء هنا أيها الرفاق.‬
Let's fly!
‫لنُغير مكاننا.‬
I may be avaricious,
‫قد أكون محبًّا للمال،‬
but I am first and foremost a journalist!
‫لكنّني صحفيّ قبل كلّ شيء.‬
I make people dance to the tune of my lies.
‫إنني أُطرِب الناس ليرقصوا على أنغام أكاذيبي.‬
I'm a DJ of words!
‫أنا أشبه بمنسّق أغانٍ للكلمات!‬
I decide what to publish!
‫أنا من يقرّر ما أنشره!‬
Mr. Morgans!
‫مورغانز-سان! وصلتك مكالمة من الملك وابول من مملكة الطبل...‬
King Wapol?
‫الملك وابول؟‬
What does he want?
‫ما الّذي يريده؟‬
Well, it sounds like he has information to leak.
‫نعم، يبدو أنّه يرغب في تسريب معلومات.‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟!‬
What's going on?
‫ما الّذي يحدث؟‬
A special report?
‫تقرير خاصّ؟‬
Don't worry...
‫لا تقلقي...‬
It'll be all right.
‫سنكون بخير...‬
With the government's failure to hush up what had happened,
‫إضافة إلى الحادثة الّتي فشلت الحكومة في التستّر عليها،‬
the decisions the leaders made at the Reverie, as well as the incidents that occurred there,
‫فالقرارات التي توصّل إليها القادة في مؤتمر «ليفيلي» والحوادث الّتي وقعت هناك‬
instantly became known throughout the world and left many people in shock.
‫أمسيتا معروفتين في كلّ أرجاء العالم في لمح البصر وأصابتا الشعوب بالصدمة‬
Vayyt!
‫مهلًا، ما الغاية من كلّ هذا؟!‬
Revolutionary Army Headquarters Kamabakka Queendom
‫مقر الجيش الثوري‬ ‫مملكة كاماباكا‬
This cannot be true!
‫لا يعقل أنّ هذا صحيح!‬
It is just a story in the paper, right?
‫إنها مجرّد مقالة منشورة في الصحيفة، صحيح؟!‬
That is just the WEN! Their bird president must have written nonsense!
‫إنها صحيفة الاقتصاد العالمية! لا بدّ أن رئيسها الطّائر ذاك يكتب هراءً ليس إلّا!‬
I am sure of it!
‫أنا واثق من ذلك!‬
This is Sabo after all!
‫إنّه سابو، هذا مستحيل...‬
I do not buy it!
‫أنا... لا أصدّق هذا!‬
Calm down!
‫اهدأ!‬
First, we must confirm the facts.
‫علينا التّأكّد من الحقائق أوّلًا.‬
But with all of them out of contact...
‫لكن لا يمكن الاتّصال بأيٍّ منهم... كيف لنا أن نتأكّد؟‬
It's not true, is it?
‫هذه محض كذبة، صحيح...‬
Sabo...
‫يا سابو-كن؟...‬
Royal Escort Ship Kingdom of Goa
‫السفينة الملكية‬ ‫مملكة غوا‬
My lady!
‫يا سيّدتي!‬
He was in Mary Geoise?!
‫كان في ماريجوا؟!‬
M-My brother?!
‫أ-أخي الكبير؟!‬
Windmill Village Kingdom of Goa
‫قرية فوشا‬ ‫بمملكة غوا‬
What happened to Makino?
‫ما الّذي حلّ بماكينو؟‬
The bar is closed today.
‫الحانة مغلقة اليوم.‬
So much has happened in the world...
‫كانت هنالك أخبار كثيرة في العالم...‬
I could use a drink.
‫أحتاج لمشروب الآن.‬
Sabo is...
‫إنّ سابو-كُن...‬
Mt. Colubo Kingdom of Goa
‫جبل كوربو‬ ‫بمملكة غوا‬
And I had just learned he was still alive...
‫لم أعرف أنه حيًّا إلا قريبًا...‬
Tell me it's not true!
‫أخبروني أنّ هذا كذب!‬
Sabo!
‫سابو!‬
Undersea Prison Impel Down
‫السجن القابع في أعماق البحر‬ ‫إمبل داون‬
I never get bored with this world!
‫لا أملّ أبدًا من هذا العالم،‬
It's getting interesting!
‫بدأت الأمور تصبح أكثر متعة!‬
Hey, guys!
‫أيها الرجال،‬
Beehive Pirate Island
‫جزيرة القراصنة‬ ‫هاتشينوس‬
Let's set sail!
‫لنُبحر!‬
Instead of watching the Marines snatch it away,
‫بدلًا من مشاهدة الحكومة وهي تضع يدها عليها،‬
I'll take it for myself!
‫فسآخذها لنفسي!‬
And now, we return to the present...
‫والآن، نعود للحاضر...‬
The Outskirts of Ebisu Town Wano
‫بلاد وانو‬ ‫ضواحي‬ ‫بلدة إبيسو‬
Koby, it's me.
‫إنه أنا يا كوبي.‬
Present Day A Stretch of Open Sea
‫في الحاضر،‬ ‫في بحرٍ ما‬
Hold on a second.
‫تمهّل لحظةً.‬
Let me go somewhere private.
‫لا يمكنني التحدث معك هنا.‬
Okay.
‫حسنًا.‬
Oh, yeah! Sea!
‫صحيح، «بحر!»‬
Fog!
‫«ضباب!»‬
As always,
‫متشددٌ كعادتك.‬
Well, it is a rule...
‫حسنٌ، إنّها قاعدة...‬
Oh, right! It's terrible!
‫صحيح، هناك أمر فظيع!‬
There's something I need to report to you,
‫ثمّة أمر عليّ أن أبلغك به...‬
Commander!
‫أيها القبطان!‬
X Drake Marine Headquarters Officer of SWORD, a Top Secret Special Force
‫ديس دريك‬ ‫نقيب في منظمة سورد‬ ‫وحدة خاصة فائقة السرية‬ ‫ضمن مقر البحرية‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟! أهذا هو الوضع هناك؟!‬
Yeah. Even with all the Marines in the world
‫نعم، إنّه أكثر ممّا يمكن استيعابه...‬
it's too much to handle.
‫حتّى بوجود كلّ جنود البحريّة في العالم...‬
Captain Koby Marine Headquarters Member of SWORD
‫كوبي‬ ‫عقيد في البحرية‬ ‫وعضو في منظمة سورد‬
So just as we planned,
‫لذلك كما خطّطنا، لن تتدخّل البحريّة فيما يحدث هناك.‬
They don't have enough manpower.
‫ليس لديهم جنود بما يكفي...‬
That's fine.
‫لا بأس بذلك في اعتقادي فبلاد وانو ليست تابعة لحكومة العالم‬
Now, about Big Mom arriving at Onigashima...
‫والآن، بشأن وصول بيغ مام لأونيغاشيما...‬
Yes.
‫نعم.‬
Kaido and Big Mom have been at odds for so long
‫كان هنالك صراع بين كايدو وبيغ مام منذ مدّة طويلة...‬
that the Marines are hoping those two pirates will ruin each other.
‫تتوقّع البحريّة أن يدمّر هؤلاء القراصنة بعضهم.‬
Yeah, I guess.
‫أظنّ ذلك.‬
As we expected, Kaido and Big Mom were at each other's throats...
‫كما توقّعنا، فكلّ من كايدو وبيغ مام كان يتربّص للآخر...‬
but now they've joined hands!
‫لكنّهما تحالفا معًا!‬
Wh-Wh-Wh-What do you mean?!
‫ما-ما-ما-ماذا تقصد؟!‬
As for Straw Hat Luffy, there's been no word of a breakout.
‫بالنّسبة لقبّعة القشّ لوفي فلم ترد أخبار عن أيّ واقعة هروب.‬
The situation is at a standstill.
‫ما زال الوضع كما هو.‬
There's also one more unpleasant thing.
‫وثمّة أمر آخر، وقد يكون غير سار.‬
I saw Cipher Pol 0 in the capital the other day.
‫لكنني رأيتُ السايفر بول 0 في العاصمة قبل أيامٍ.‬
What?! Why are they in Wano?!
‫ماذا؟! لماذا هم في بلاد وانو؟!‬
I hope I'm wrong,
‫آمل أن أكون مخطئًا،‬
but it must mean the World Government
‫لكن لا بدّ أنّ ذلك يعني أنّ حكومة العالم تتعاون...‬
is doing business with Wano, a country ruled by a pirate.
‫مع بلاد وانو هذه الّتي يحكمها قرصان.‬
When I found out,
‫عندما عرفتُ عن الأمر،‬
I was stunned for a few minutes.
‫تسمّرت في مكاني...‬
By the way, where are you now?
‫بالمناسبة، أين أنت الآن؟‬
Right.
‫صحيح.‬
We're heading toward the Isle of Women...
‫بهدف القبض على إمبراطورة القراصنة بوا هانكوك...‬
to capture Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
‫انطلقنا باتّجاه جزيرة النّساء!‬
Oh, my...
‫هذا حقيقيّ...‬
Those ships coming toward us over the Calm Belt...
‫تلك السّفن المتجهة نحونا التي تعبر الحزام الهادئ...‬
Is that a Marine fleet?!
‫تعود لأسطول البحريّة؟!‬
Marguerite!
‫مارغريت!‬
What's going to happen?!
‫ما الّذي سيحدث؟!‬
The news spread all around the world.
‫الأخبار الّتي انتشرت في العالم...‬
They should have done this a long time ago!
‫كان عليهم التّخلّص من ذلك النّظام اللّعين منذ مدّة طويلة!‬
It was a mistake to team up with pirates...
‫كان التّعاون مع القراصنة خطأً من الأساس...‬
They're evil!
‫إنّهم أشرار!‬
For those who think all pirates are bad...
‫بالنّسبة للظانين أنّ كلّ القراصنة أشرار...‬
Those government dogs will finally go away!
‫كلاب الحكومة أولئك سيختفون أخيرًا!‬
Screw that Pirate Empress, Hawk Eye, and Clown!
‫سُحقًا لإمبراطورة القراصنة وعين الصّقر والمهرّج.‬
They're nothing but looters!
‫ما هم إلّا لصوص!‬
...and for those who hate looters, it's good news.
‫وبالنّسبة للّذين يكرهون اللّصوص فقد كانت أخبارًا سارّة‬
But I thought they did great in the Summit War!
‫لكنّني اعتقدتُ أنّهم أبلوا حسنًا في حرب القمّة.‬
That's what they decided?!
‫اتّخذَ القرار في مؤتمر ليفيلي؟!‬
The Marines are ready to take immediate action.
‫أعتقد أنّ تحركات البحريّة ستبدأ حالًا.‬
Is this really wise?
‫أسيكون كلّ شيء بخير؟‬
They were one of the world's three great powers!
‫لقد كانوا إحدى القوى الثّلاث العظمى في العالم!‬
For those who knew of their feats in the Summit War,
‫وبالنسبة لأولئك الّذي عرفوا كيف أبلوا في حرب القمّة،‬
and those who were concerned about disrupting the balance of the three great powers,
‫وأولئك القلقين بشأن فقدان توازن القوى الثلاث العظمى،‬
it was truly an alarming situation.
‫كان هذا وضعًا مقلقًا بحقّ.‬
The news story from the latest Reverie that stunned people across the world the most...
‫إحدى الأخبار النّاجمة عن آخر مؤتمر «ليفيلي،»‬
was...
‫كان...‬
the abolition...
‫إلغاء...‬
of the Seven Warlords system!
‫نظام الشيتشيبوكاي!‬
The Seven Warlords of the Sea were pirates officially recognized by the government.
‫الشيتشيبوكاي هم قراصنةٌ مُعترف بهم رسميًّا من حكومة العالم.‬
While they were allowed to pillage,
‫مع أنّ النهب مسموح لهم،‬
the government used them as deterrents against other pirates.
‫فالحكومة تستغلهم بمثابة رادع ضدّ القراصنة الآخرين.‬
The roster of the Seven Warlords has changed over time.
‫تغيّرت تشكيلة الشيتشيبوكاي باستمرار مع مرور الوقت.‬
Crocodile.
‫كروكودايل.‬
He clashed with the Straw Hats over the Kingdom of Alabasta.
‫فقد تصادم مع طاقم قبّعة القشّ بشأن مملكة أرباستا سابقًا.‬
He was trying to take over the kingdom
‫كان يحاول الاستيلاء على المملكة‬
but was ultimately defeated by Luffy and expelled from the Seven Warlords.
‫لكنّه هُزم على يد لوفي وطُرد من الشيتشيبوكاي.‬
The man who replaced Crocodile and joined the Seven Warlords...
‫الرّجل الّذي حلّ محلّ كروكودايل وانضمّ للشّيتشيبوكاي...‬
was Marshall D. Teach.
‫كان مارشال دي تيتش.‬
However, he announced his resignation after achieving his goal.
‫ولكنه أعلن عن استقالته بعد تحقيقه لهدفه.‬
Jinbe, Knight of the Sea,
‫الّذي عارض حرب القمّة،‬
opposed the Summit War and grew disdainful of the Marines.
‫وأصبح عدوًّا للبحرية، «فارس البحر جينبي.»‬
He, too, declared his resignation.
‫قدّم هو الآخر استقالته.‬
Gecko Moria.
‫غيكّو موريا،‬
This man who had once clashed with the Straw Hats was also called to the Summit War.
‫اعترض هذا الرّجل طريق طاقم قبّعة القشّ سابقًا واستُدعي لحرب القمّة أيضًا.‬
However...
‫ولكن...‬
just after the war, an order for an ambush came from high up in the government,
‫بعد الحرب، هوجم على حين غرّة نزولًا عند أمر من كبار المسؤولين في الحكومة،‬
and he was expelled.
‫وطُرد من الشيتشيبوكاي.‬
Heavenly Demon Donquixote Doflamingo.
‫الشيطان السّماويّ دونكيهوتي دوفلامينغو...‬
All while governing Dressrosa as its king,
‫في نفس الوقت الّذي حكم فيه دريسروزا ملكًا لها،‬
he trafficked an artificial devil fruit, SMILE, as an influential underground broker.
‫كان يهرّب فواكه الشيطان الاصطناعيّة المعروفة بـ«سمايل» وسيطًا مؤثّر خلف الظّلال‬
However...
‫ولكنه...‬
he lost the kingdom in a struggle against Luffy's alliance,
‫خسر المعركة للسّيطرة على المملكة ضدّ لوفي والبقيّة،‬
and his title of Warlord was revoked.
‫وسُحب منه لقب الشيتشيبوكاي.‬
And finally, Trafalgar Law.
‫وأخيرًا، ترافالغار لاو.‬
He allied himself with the Straw Hats to take down Doflamingo...
‫لغاية الإطاحة بدوفلامينغو، تحالف مع طاقم قبعة القش وسُحب لقبه منه أيضًا.‬
The four pirates who reign supreme as if they're emperors:
‫القراصنة الأربعة الّذين يفرضون سيطرتهم أباطرةً.‬
the Four Emperors.
‫الأباطرة الأربعة.‬
And trying to contain them: Marine Headquarters.
‫مقر البحرية الذي يحاول احتواءهم.‬
Last but not least: The Seven Warlords of the Sea.
‫إضافةً إلى الشيتشيبوكاي.‬
The Seven Warlords of the Sea
‫الشيتشيبوكاي‬
These three great powers have kept the world at peace.
‫حافظت هذه القوى الثلاث العظمى على السّلام في العالم.‬
The Four Emperors Navy
‫البحرية الأباطرة الأربعة‬
However,
‫ولكن...‬
two kings had suffered terribly at the hands of Warlords:
‫ثمّة ملكان تكبّدا خسائر فادحة على يد الشيتشيبوكاي.‬
King Nefertari Cobra of the Kingdom of Alabasta,
‫الملك نيفرتاري كوبرا من مملكة أرباستا،‬
and Riku Doldo III of the Kingdom of Dressrosa.
‫والملك ريكو دولدو الثّالث من مملكة دريسروزا.‬
They fought for the abolition of the Seven Warlords system.
‫لقد كافحا في سبيل إلغاء نظام الشيتشيبوكاي.‬
Then, after a heated debate at the Reverie,
‫وبعد نقاش حامٍ في مؤتمر «ليفيلي،»‬
a large majority supported the proposition, and it passed.
‫دعمت أغلبيّة ساحقة هذا الاقتراح وصادقوا عليه.‬
Therefore, the Seven Warlords of the Sea will automatically be stripped of all their rights,
‫وبموجبه سيتنازل كلّ الشيتشيبوكاي عن كلّ حقوقهم طبعًا،‬
and their connection with the World Government will hereby be cut off.
‫وعلاقاتهم مع حكومة العالم ستُقطع.‬
That means...!
‫ممّا يعني!...‬
Empty Bluffs Island New World
‫جزيرة كارايباري‬ ‫بالعالم الجديد‬
Buggy,
‫يا باغي،‬
you're just another pirate!
‫ما أنت إلا قرصان عادي الآن.‬
That's no fair, you assholes!
‫هذا ليس عادلًا أيها المغفّلون!‬
A decision was made without telling us, and since we're no longer useful, you arrest us?!
‫اتُّخِذ القرار من دون إخطارنا، وبما أنّنا لم نعد مفيدين ستعتقلوننا؟‬
You have no sense of justice whatsoever!
‫لا تتمتعون بحسّ عدالة على الإطلاق!‬
Whether Crocodile and Doflamingo outsmarted you is none of my business!
‫لا علاقة لتحايل كروكودايل وَدوفلامينغو عليكم بعملي.‬
Don't take it out on me!
‫لا تنفّسوا عن غضبكم عليّ!‬
They've got the whole coast surrounded!
‫لقد حاصَرَوا الساحل بأكمله.‬
What should we do?
‫ماذا علينا فعله؟‬
My entire life's plan is going to the dogs!
‫ذهبت خطّة حياتي بأكملها أدراج الرّياح.‬
Oh?
‫ماذا؟‬
An Island in the New World
‫إحدى جزر‬ ‫العالم الجديد‬
The Marines should be on our side, but they've surrounded us!
‫يُفترض أن تكون البحريّة إلى جانبنا لكنّنا محاصرون!‬
What should we do, Mommy?!
‫ماذا علينا فعله يا ماما؟!‬
Mommy!
‫يا ماما!‬
The Ruins of the Muggy Kingdom Gloom Island
‫أطلال «مملكة شيكيارو»‬ ‫بجزيرة كورايغانا‬
Surrender yourself now,
‫سلّم نفسك،‬
Hawk Eye Mihawk!
‫يا عين الصقر ميهوك.‬
Surrender yourself now!
‫سلّم نفسك!‬
The Isle of Women Amazon Lily
‫جزيرة النساء‬ ‫أمازون ليلي‬
Snyake Princess, we have a problem!
‫لدينا مصيبة يا أميرة الأفاعي!‬
Your title of Warlord has been stripped away!
‫سُحبَ منك لقب الشيتشيبوكاي!‬
Elder Nyon!
‫أيّتها الجدّة نيون،‬
There are Marine ships off the coast!
‫ثمّة سفن تابعة للبحريّة على السّاحل!‬
What?!
‫ماذا قلتِ؟!‬
They've already gone into action?!
‫بدؤوا تحرّكاتهم بهذه السرعة؟!‬
Don't panic!
‫لا تهلعن!‬
Snyake Princess!
‫أميرة الأفاعي..‬
They've obviously forgotten something...
‫أعتقد أنّهم قد نسوا أمرًا...‬
This is no good, President Buggy!
‫لا فائدة أيّها الرّئيس باغي.‬
Should we run?!
‫هل نلوذ بالفرار؟!‬
Of course not! We'll show them a flashy fight!
‫بالطّبع سنقاتلهم بطريقة مبهرجة!‬
Show some guts, you sad sacks!
‫أظهروا بعض الجرأة أيها الحمقى!‬
– That's our President Buggy!
‫هذا هو رئيسنا باغي!‬
Former Warlord of the Sea
‫شيتشيبوكاي سابق‬
Buggy's Delivery Chairman Buggy "the Bombastic Clown"
‫الرئيس باغي «المهرج النجم»‬
Buggy's Delivery Chairman Buggy "the Bombastic Clown"
‫النجم الرئيس باغي «المهرج «الرئيس باغي «المهرج النجم شركة باغي للتوصيل»‬
– Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
‫باغي! باغي! باغي! باغي!‬
Former Warlord of the Sea
‫شيتشيبوكاي سابق‬
Seems like they're not on our side anymore!
‫يبدو أنّهم ما عادوا في صفّنا!‬
How incredibly unforgivable...
‫هذا لا يُغتفر...‬
Weevil!
‫ويفل! أمنحك الإذن للإطاحة بهم!‬
R-Really?!
‫حـ-حقًّا؟‬
In that case, I'm gonna kill 'em...
‫سأقتلهم إذًا...‬
Edward "Whitebeard Jr. (Self-Proclaimed)" Weevil Former Warlord of the Sea
‫إدوارد «ابن اللحية البيضاء المزعوم» ويفل‬ ‫شيتشيبوكاي سابق‬
in the name of Whitebeard!
‫باسم اللحية البيضاء.‬
I feel a tremor of excitement.
‫أشعر برعشة حماس...‬
It's been a long time...
‫لقد مرّ وقت طويل...‬
Dracule Mihawk "Hawk Eye" Former Warlord of the Sea
‫شيتشيبوكاي‬ ‫سابق دراكيول ميهوك‬ ‫«عين الصقر»‬
Former Warlord
‫شيتشيبوكاي‬ ‫سابق‬
Dracule Mihawk
‫دراكيول ميهوك‬
"Hawk Eye" Former Warlord of the Sea
‫شيتشيبوكاي‬ ‫سابق دراكيول ميهوك‬ ‫«عين الصقر»‬
since I was the one being hunted.
‫مذ كنتُ أنا من يُطارَد.‬
Dracule Mihawk "Hawk Eye" Former Warlord of the Sea
‫شيتشيبوكاي‬ ‫سابق دراكيول ميهوك‬ ‫«عين الصقر»‬
We became the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
‫أصبحنا أعضاء في الشيتشيبوكاي...‬
"Pirate Empress" Boa Hancock Former Warlord of the Sea
‫بوا هانكوك «إمبراطورة القراصنة»‬ ‫شيتشيبوكاي سابقة‬
Former Warlord of the Sea "Pirate Empress" Boa Hancock
‫شيتشيبوكاي سابقة شيتشيبوكاي سابقة‬
because of our might!
‫لأنّنا أقوياء!‬
I'm counting on you guys.
‫أعتمد عليكم يا رفاق!‬
In the meantime...
‫وبينما تفعلون ذلك...‬
I'll get the hell out of here...
‫سأنفذ بجلدي من هنا!‬